# Joseph Supples

Seattle, Washington, United States



joseph.craig94@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/joseph-supples

# **Summary**

Senior in a practicum focused Bachelor's program for Computer Science / Application Development at North Seattle - 3.99 GPA.

Phyllis A Mayo Scholarship, Lloyd International Honors College, Reynolds Scholarship, '21-'22 Guided Pathways Advisory Council Student Member

Full Stack Developer @ Frontrunner - Backend: Django, Frontend: Flutter.

Previously, Software Development Engineer Intern at Amazon - worked on regionalization of payment services.

Proficient in HTML, CSS, JS, JAVA, React, Python, and familiar with Kotlin, SQL, Ruby, and Flutter.

## **Experience**



## **Software Engineer**

FrontRunner

Oct 2022 - Present (1 month +)

Full Stack (Backend - Django, Frontend - Flutter)

- Implement UI and backend based on Figma designs and functionality specifications



## Software Developer (Practicum)

Floop Edu

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022 (3 months)

- Worked as a part of an agile software dev team to implement requested features.
- Primarily utilized React and Firebase for development
- Used Cypress for QA / testing.

# \*

#### **IDEAL Senior Fellow**

Washington State Board for Community and Technical Colleges

Jan 2022 - May 2022 (5 months)

- Mentored a cohort of community college students as they navigate the IDEAL program.
- Assisted them as they prepared presentations for their respective educational institutions regarding inequitable practices and procedures.



#### **Software Development Engineer Intern**

Amazon

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022 (4 months)

- Worked on regionalization of payment services
- Researched and developed POC for an internal tool

- Configured test cases and implemented request routing

#### **Education**



# North Seattle College

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Application Development 2021 - 2023

# University of North Carolina at Greensboro

Undergraduate Study (~ Associate's Degree equivalent credits), Computer Science and Theatre

2012 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Java Basic Certificate - HackerRank

e8ff364c3336

#### **Skills**

Front-end Development • Java • JavaScript • Back-End Web Development • React.js • Ruby • Full-Stack Development • Python (Programming Language) • Django • Flutter

## **Honors & Awards**



Phyllis A. Mayo Schlarship - North Seattle College



IDEAL Fellow - Seattle Colleges

Aug 2021

IDEAL Fellowship wherein I was certified to use the IMPACT toolkit to evaluate policies and advise through equity and antiracist lenses.

Dean's List - Seattle Colleges

Jul 2021

**Lloyd International Honors College** - University of North Carolina - Greensboro

Honors College at UNC-Greensboro

**Katherine Z. Reynolds Scholarship** - UNC-G: Lloyd International Honors College 2012

Scholarship awarded by UNC-Greensboro Lloyd International Honors College